{
    "subject": "resource/Claudio_Bieler",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Santa_Fe_Province",
    "human_readable": "Claudio Bieler was born in Santa Fe Province.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9000324010848999,
            "question": "Where was Claudio Bieler born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5604068636894226,
            "question": "What province is Santa Fe Province in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37732112407684326,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Santa Fe Province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2981184720993042,
            "question": "What kind of culture exists in Santa Fe Province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29398736357688904,
            "question": "Is Claudio Bieler Argentinian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28802624344825745,
            "question": "Is Santa Fe Province a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24849656224250793,
            "question": "What do you know about Claudio Bieler's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2461370825767517,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Santa Fe Province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16861049830913544,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Santa Fe Province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14378726482391357,
            "question": "Could Claudio Bieler have a connection to Argentina?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Claudio Bieler was born in Santa Fe Province.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2631_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Santa Fe Province?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2631_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Santa Fe Province?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2631_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do you know about Claudio Bieler's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2631_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2631_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Claudio Bieler was born in Vera, Argentina.  There is no mention of him being born in Santa Fe Province. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nReasoning:\n\nThe provided documents contain information about Claudio Bieler's biography, football career, and stats. However, none of the documents mention his birthplace as Santa Fe Province.\n\nDocument 1 and Document 2 state that he was born in Vera, Argentina.\nDocument 3 states that he was born in Vera (no specific province mentioned).\nDocument 4 mentions Vera, Argentina as Claudio Bieler's birthplace but again does not specify a province."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information to support the claim that Claudio Bieler was born in Santa Fe Province. The context mentions he was born in Vera, Argentina, but does not specify which province it is located in."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Claudio Bieler was born in Vera, Argentina, not Santa Fe Province.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information states he made his professional debut with Col\u00f3n de Santa Fe, but also mentions he played for Atl\u00e9tico Rafaela where he led the league with sixteen goals.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the context information states that Claudio Bieler was born in Vera, which is not mentioned as being in Santa Fe Province.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that Claudio Bieler was born in Vera, Argentina, not Santa Fe Province.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}